<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Luyao &quot;Lulu&quot; Wang</title>
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://luyao-wang.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-09-26T22:12:17.000Z</updated>
  <id>https://luyao-wang.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Luyao &quot;Lulu&quot; Wang</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Brief Introduction</title>
    <link href="https://luyao-wang.github.io/2017/09/26/brief-introduction/"/>
    <id>https://luyao-wang.github.io/2017/09/26/brief-introduction/</id>
    <published>2017-09-26T22:05:25.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-09-26T22:12:17.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi I’m <code>Looloo</code>. I’ll be your supplemental Instruction (SI) Leader for this quarter. I am a proud member of this great organization called SCAA <a href="http://scaa.csueastbay.edu/" target="_blank" rel="external">(Student Center for Academic Achievement)</a>.</p>
<p>I took CS 3560 Introduction to Systems Programming with Professor Stalica Summer 2017 quarter. Professor Stalica is extremely awesome, super chill and helpful. I really look forward to work with him to help you learn and succeed in this course.</p>
<p>Throughout this quarter, I will put up <code>discussion session materials</code> on this website.</p>
<p>About myself, I am a graduate student in Computer Science. This is my third quarter at CSUEB. I took my Data Structures and Algorithms Spring 2017 quarter with Dr. Varick Erickson. If you would like to know more about me, feel free to click on the About tab.</p>
<p>I will be hosting discussion session <code>twice</code> a week (one discussion session per lecture). Around Midterm and Final, I will also be hosting <code>extra review sessions</code> to help you prepare for the exams.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;Hi I’m &lt;code&gt;Looloo&lt;/code&gt;. I’ll be your supplemental Instruction (SI) Leader for this quarter. I am a proud member of this great organiz
    
    </summary>
    
      <category term="logistics" scheme="https://luyao-wang.github.io/categories/logistics/"/>
    
    
      <category term="logistics" scheme="https://luyao-wang.github.io/tags/logistics/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
